Charioce!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)シャリオ～～ス！
(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)ギュッてして！
Hug me!
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)これが 赤い竜…｡
So this is the red dragon.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
まるで 小さなバハムートだな｡
Her dragon is like a small Bahamut.
昨日のこと➡
Promise not to tell anybody about yesterday!
絶対 誰にも言わないで！
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)お前は 俺に➡
-Let me make love to you and turn you into a dragon!
-What?!
抱かれて竜になれ｡
抱かれ…｡
Are you ready to help me battle the gods,
どうだ？
神と戦う覚悟はできたか？
聖女ジャンヌ･ダルク殿｡
Saint Jeanne D'arc?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
魔族の失った誇りを取り戻す｡➡
I will take back the pride the demons have lost.
そのときが来たのだ｡
The time has come.
Do you know the meaning
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
次に２つの月が重なるとき➡
その日が なんの日か分かるか？➡
of the next time when two moons align?
５年前
魔都コキュートスが陥落し➡
On that day five years ago,
the demon capital of Cocytus fell,
俺たち魔族が
人間どもに屈した日だ｡➡
and we demons bowed to the humans.
戦勝記念などと
浮かれているヤツらに➡
I will teach a lesson to those who would treat
that day as a victory celebration.
今こそ 思い知らせてやる｡
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)何をする気だ？
What are you planning on doing?
人間の王を殺す｡
I will slay the king of men.
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)ふふふっ｡
そんなことができるのなら➡
If you're able to do that,
then why were we defeated five years ago?
５年前 なぜ 俺たちは敗れた？
That's right! We weren't able
to defeat the humans with our magic!
そうだ｡ 俺たちの魔力では
人間たちを倒せなかった｡
ヤツらが神から奪った あの力で➡
Have you forgotten how many of us
the humans killed
大勢の仲間がやられたのを
忘れたのか｡
with the power they stole from the gods?!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)その力を打ち破る｡
I will destroy their power.
(悪魔たち)なっ…｡
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)どうやって？
How?
I'm sure even you have heard the rumors
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)貴様らも うわさぐらいは
聞いたことがあるだろう｡➡
圧倒的な力で
人間どもを蹴散らし➡
about the dragon who routed the humans with
overwhelming power and sent the capital in a panic?
王都を騒がす竜のことを｡
(悪魔たち)あっ…｡
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)まさか…｡
You don't mean...
We use the red dragon.
赤い竜を使う｡
Rage of Bahamut
≪これ ２つ買ったらさ➡
If I buy two of these, will you give me a deal?
安くしてくれる？
今日は 半額の日だから➡
They're already half price today.
That's all the discount I can give you.
これ以上は まけられないよ｡
ええ～？
Then how about arm-wrestling me?
じゃあさ 私と腕相撲しない？
腕相撲？
Arm-wrestle you?
私が勝ったら 半額の半額でどう？
If I win, how about you make it
half off half price?
ねえねえ お願い｡
う～ん…｡
Come on, please?
うっ ぐっ！ ああ～ あっ！
ドサッ！
コン！(靴が当たる音)
痛っ！
Ow!
(店員)いかがですか？ お客様｡
How are you finding things, miss?
ふふっ ふふん ふふふふっ｡
It suits you.
(店員)よくお似合いです｡
マジっすか？
Seriously?
ムガロちゃん ちゃんと着れた？
わあ～！
Mugaro, did you put it on?
ムガロちゃん かわいいです～！
You're so cute, Mugaro!
やっぱり 女の子は
これぐらいフリフリしなきゃ｡
Girls look so much better in frilly dresses!
なんで アザゼルは
あんなかわいくない服を➡
Why did Azazel make you wear that boring outfit?
ムガロちゃんに
着せてたのかしら？
まったく バカ悪魔なんだから｡
He's such a stupid demon.
王都で買い物するの初めてだから
ついつい いっぱい買っちゃったな｡
This was my first time shopping in the capital,
so I really went overboard.
仕送りの余り
ほとんど使っちゃった…➡
I spent most of the money I had left over.
ってことは内密でお願いします｡
So I need you to keep this between us!
楽しかった？ ふふっ｡
Did you have fun?
ムガロちゃんって
ほんとにいい子だね ふふふっ｡
You're such a good girl, Mugaro!
アザゼルが ムガロちゃんと
いつも一緒にいたのは➡
I bet that's why Azazel always had you around.
そういうとこが好きだったんだね
きっと｡
I hope he comes back soon.
あいつ 早く戻ってくるといいね｡
Damn it.
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)んっ！ こんな所で
油売ってる暇はねぇんだ｡➡
I don't have time for your loafing!
早く立て！
ドカッ ドカッ ドカッ…(蹴る音)
Get up already!
What's with that look?
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)なんだ？ その目は｡
フォレスト…｡
うっ ぐわっ！
フォレスト フォレスト…｡
うっ ぐわっ ああっ！
あぁ…｡
≪やめなさいよ！
(２人)あっ｡
Stop that!
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)
何か用かい？ お嬢ちゃん｡
You want something, little girl?
ほっときなよ お嬢ちゃん｡
関わんない方がいいよ｡
Just look the other way, girl!
I wouldn't get involved.
そんなひどいことしたら
その人 死んじゃうじゃない｡
If you keep that up, he's going to die.
お嬢ちゃん
何を勘違いしてるのか知らねぇが➡
Little girl,
I don't know what's gotten into your head,
but this isn't a person.
こいつは人じゃあねぇ｡ 悪魔だ｡➡
It's a demon and my slave.
そして 俺の奴隷だ｡
俺の奴隷を どう扱おうが➡
And what I do with my slave
is my business, isn't it?
俺の勝手だろ？ ん？
だからって
苦しめていいわけないでしょ｡
That doesn't mean you can torture him.
そんなことも分からないの？
Or are you too stupid to know that?
Little girl, you keep this up
and I'll make you my slave too.
お嬢ちゃん
あんまり面倒なこと言ってると➡
俺の奴隷にしちまうよ｡
何よ｡ あんたたち
やれるもんなら やってみなさいよ｡
What?
Feel free to try.
いい度胸だ｡ かわいがってやる｡
You've got guts!
We'll show you a good time.
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)
あっ な… なんだ？ えっ！➡
What?
どうなってる!?
(市民たち)あっ ああっ！
What the hell is going on!
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)フォレスト
フォレスト フォレスト…｡
ぐおぉ～！
(悪魔たち)ぐおぉ～！
Mugaro, did you do something?
ムガロちゃん 今 何かした？
どうしたん？
What is it?
I definitely sensed it.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)
反応があったのは間違いない｡
この辺りを捜せ｡
Search the area.
どうしたの？ ムガロちゃん｡
What's wrong, Mugaro?
Are you hungry or something?
おなかすいたの？ ん？
≫(隊長)
王都に不審な動きをする者たちが｡
There are suspicious individuals in the capital.
(隊長)魔力の反応は
察知できておりません｡
But we are unable to detect any magic from them.
神か｡
(隊長)おそらくは➡
-Gods?
-Most likely.
例の子供を
捜しているのではないかと｡
I believe they are looking for the child.
やはり 動きだしたか｡
So they have taken action as I thought.
What shall we do?
(隊長)いかがいたしましょう？
放っておけ｡
Ignore them.
包帯悪魔を処理する方が先だ｡
(隊長)はっ｡
-Dealing with the rag demon takes priority.
-Yes, My Lord.
包帯悪魔を追えば いずれ
その子供にも たどりつける｡
If we pursue the rag demon,
he will eventually lead us to the child.
(隊長)御意｡
As you command.
Rage of Bahamut
(兵士たち)はあっ はあっ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)それまで！
That's enough!
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)アレサンド
なぜ 稽古に参加しない？
Alessand, why aren't you participating in training?
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)調子悪いんで｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)どこが悪い？
I feel a bit off.
What's wrong?
心っすかね｡
It's just this feeling.
ふぅ～｡
ディアスさん➡
Dias, why did I ever join the Orleans Knights?
なんで 俺 この騎士団に
入っちゃったんすかね？
I really looked up to Saint Jeanne D'arc.
俺 聖女ジャンヌ･ダルク様に
憧れてたんすよ｡
すごい美人だっていうし｡➡
Not to mention she was an incredible beauty.
But by the time I joined, she was gone.
それなのに ここに入ったら
もう ジャンヌ様いなくて➡
いたのは 変な髪型の団長だし｡
Instead, I got a captain with weird hair.
You still don't understand the kind of man
Captain Kaisar is.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)お前は ｶｲｻﾞﾙ団長のことを
まだ分かっていない｡➡
He has more integrity than you give him credit for.
あの人は お前が思っているより
ずっと骨のある男だ｡➡
He's even one of the heroes who protected the capital
from the demon army ten years ago.
10年前 悪魔の軍から王都を守った
英雄の一人でもある｡➡
That's how he joined the Orleans Knights.
その功績で
オルレアン騎士団に加わったのだ｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)でも それ 昔でしょ？➡
But that's the past.
今日だって どこに行ったんだか｡
Where is he even at today?
ガアッ ガアッ
You're sure gloomy.
(ﾘﾀ)なんか暗くない？
Rita, would you hear me out for a bit?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)
リタ 私の話を聞いてくれるか？
What?
何よ？
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)できれば➡
I had wanted to keep these feelings to myself.
ずっと
心の内に秘めておきたかった｡
Huh?
ダン！(ﾃｰﾌﾞﾙをたたく音)
私の今の本心を…➡
I have to tell you how I really feel.
他の誰にも言えない
本当の気持ちを➡
These are feelings I could
only share with you.
リタに聞いてほしいのだ｡
ど ど… どうしたのよ？ 急に｡
What's gotten into you?
リタ｡
はい｡
-Rita.
-Yes?
I...
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)私は…➡
オルレアン騎士団団長に
ふさわしい男なのだろうか？
I'm worthy of being a captain
in the Orleans Knights, right?
(ﾘﾀ)ちっ…｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)最近➡
Recently some of the younger members
have started to become dissatisfied.
騎士団の若者の間に
不満を持つ者が現れはじめた｡
不満に思う気持ちも分かる｡
確かに 昔ほど➡
I can understand their dissatisfaction.
If I were asked if the Orleans Knights possess
the same glory as they have in the past,
騎士団として輝かしい栄光を
感じられるかというと➡
今は不遇のときだ｡
I would have to answer no.
Perhaps it's inevitable that the Orleans Knights,
神のご加護の下 戦った
オルレアン騎士団が➡
who once fought with the blessing of the gods
are looked down upon now.
今の世で軽視されてしまうのは
しょうがないのかもしれない｡➡
現状を変えるには 陛下のご意思を
変えてもらうしかない｡
Changing this would require His Majesty
to change his way of thinking.
But what can a mere captain hope to do?
しかし そんなことを
一騎士団の団長に期待されても➡
応えきれない｡ そもそも
陛下のやり方は極端なのだ｡➡
Besides, His Majesty's methods are too extreme.
性急すぎる｡ アザゼルが
ああいった行動に出てしまうのも➡
I shouldn't have any understanding
for Azazel's actions, but I do!
分かってはいけないのに
私は分かってしまうのだ！➡
だが アザゼルもアザゼルだ｡➡
But Azazel is also in the wrong.
私の忠告も聞かずに
無謀なことばかり続けて｡➡
He continued his reckless actions
without heeding my warnings.
あいつは
戦うことしかできないのか！
Is violence all he's capable of?
Everyone is acting so selfishly!
誰も彼も皆 勝手なのだ！
カチャン！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)
争いが止まらないのは当然だ｡
It's no wonder the conflict won't end.
Even so, I'm trying to do what is right!
その中でも 私は やるべきことを
やろうとしているのに➡
なぜ
不満を言われなければならない！
Yet I still get complaints!
不満を言いたいのは 私の方だ…｡
If anyone should be complaining, it's me!
バキッ！
ぐおっ！
バシャーン！
ガアッ ガアッ
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)くっ… リタ なぜだ？
Rita, why?
(ﾘﾀ)あんたの話が
つまんないからよ！➡
Because you're boring me!
Honestly.
ったく｡➡
I was a little excited that you
actually invited me out to lunch.
珍しく食事に誘われたから
なんなのかと思ったけど➡
But thank you for disappointing me.
ほんと がっかりだわ｡➡
Would you have been this much
of a pathetic crybaby ten years ago?
１０年前のあんたは
そんなに ウジウジ ウジウジ➡
ウダウダしてたかしらね｡
えっ？
When I knew you ten years ago,
私が知る あのころのあんたは
バカで 思い込みが激しくって➡
you were stupid, jumped to conclusions,
and were all around pretty useless.
あんまり 役に立たなかったけど
それでも➡
But you always strove to do
what you felt was right.
まっすぐ 自分の信じる正義を
貫こうとしていた…➡
Or at least I think I remember you being that way.
こともあったような気がするけど
それも思い違いだったみたいね｡
Seems like I was wrong.
I haven't heard anything from you.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)何も報告がないが
真面目に捜しているのか？➡
Are you really looking for the child?
The child unleashed his power this afternoon.
昼に
例の子供の力が発動された｡➡
お前は何も感じなかったのか？
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あぁ～｡
Did you not sense anything?
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ？ クワッ？
ソフィエル様！
私は 神の世界に帰りたいです｡
Lady Sofiel, I want to return to Heaven!
From the bottom of my heart!
心から戻りたいです｡
私をペットにしてください｡➡
Please make me your pet!
小型で お利口 従順で 空も飛び
きっと あなた様の癒やしとして➡
I'm small and obedient and able to fly.
I'm sure I'll warm your heart!
お役に立てると存じます｡
クワッ クワッ…｡
Be quiet.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)静かにしろ｡
クワァ～！
What are you thinking?
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)何を考えているのだ？
お前 まさか ここで 一生を
過ごすつもりではあるまいな｡
You...
Don't tell me you plan to live
the rest of your life here.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)だったら悪ぃか｡
お前は そこまで堕ちたか｡
And what if I do?
Have you really fallen that far?
I don't know if you've become attached to this world,
but you're merely a fallen god.
下界に情が移ったのか知らんが
お前は所詮 堕ちた神にすぎん｡➡
Forget this foolishness
and follow my commands.
バカな考えは捨てて
私の命令に従うのだ｡ いいな｡
Understood?
≫ガチャ バタン(ﾄﾞｱの開閉音)
あぁ～｡
We're home!
ただいま～｡ って 今の人 誰？
Hey, who was that just now?
なんで あんなきれいな人が
この馬車に来たの？
Why did someone so pretty
come to this carriage?
クワァ～！
クワッ クワッ… クッ クワッ…｡
ハンサ あんたなら
知ってるでしょ？ 誰よ？
Hamsa, you know, don't you?
Who was it?
She was an old colleague of Bacchus
from a time long since passed!
遠い昔 遠い世界で
バッカスと同僚だったお方ですよ｡
同僚～？
クワッ｡
Colleague?
You don't mean lover?
恋人じゃないの～？
同僚は まあ➡
I suppose it's not that uncommon
for colleagues to become lovers.
恋人にも
なりやすいと思われますが…｡
(２人)はぁ～ん？ あはははっ！
Shut up, you idiots!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うるせぇ バカ野郎！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ｡
ねえねえ バッカス｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うるせぇって言ってんだろ！
-Hey, Bacchus.
-I told you to shut up!
ムガロちゃんって
すんごいんだ～｡ さっきね➡
Mugaro is amazing!
She chased away these awful people
who were doing terrible things to demons.
悪魔に ひどいことしてた人たちを
追っ払っちゃったんだ～｡
ムガロちゃんが
キ～ンって光ったら➡
Mugaro started glowing,
悪魔の人たちの首輪の石が
サラ～って｡
and the stones on the demons' collars
just disappeared!
クワッ！
ムガロちゃん しゃべらないから➡
Although I don't know how Mugaro did it,
since she doesn't talk.
どうやったのか分かんないけど｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あっ…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)
バッカス まさか この子が…｡
Bacchus! Could this be the child?
まさかって何？
What are you talking about?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)おい お前｡
Hey, you.
その格好は どうしたんだ？
What's with the outfit?
This is where you've been.
≫(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ここに おいででしたか｡
バハムートが現れた１０年前➡
Ten years ago when Bahamut emerged,
you were the same age as I am now.
お前は 今の私と
変わらない年齢だったであろう｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)はい｡
何をしていた？
Yes, My Lord.
What were you doing?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)
しがない賞金稼ぎをしながら➡
I traveled as a humble bounty hunter.
旅をしておりました｡
And now you are a captain in the Orleans Knights.
それが今や 騎士団の団長か｡
お前も なかなか
数奇なときを過ごしてきたのだな｡
It seems you've had a checkered life.
Yes, My Lord.
はい｡ まさか
自分が団長をやろうなどとは➡
I never would have imagined myself
becoming a captain.
みじんも考えていませんでした｡
１０年は 長かったか？
Did these ten years feel long?
There have been times it's felt long,
and times it's felt short.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)
長くもあり 短くもありました｡
そうか｡ こいつが現れたとき➡
I see.
When that thing appeared,
まだ私は 王宮に立ち入ることも
できない身分だった｡
I did not even have the status
to set foot in the palace yet.
I was the son of a lowly concubine,
卑しい妾の子であると
言われた私が➡
and it was this monster that gave me
the opportunity to be here now.
今ここにいるきっかけを
与えてくれたのは➡
この化け物だ｡
When I think of it that way, these ten years
have been checkered for me as well.
そう考えると 私の１０年も
なかなか数奇ではあるな｡
It has been a bloody ten years.
血にまみれた１０年だった｡
I've eliminated those who stood in my way of the throne,
defeated the gods, and conquered the demons.
王になるために
邪魔な人間を排除し➡
神を倒し 魔を支配した｡
But because of these ten years, the human race
was able to acquire new power.
だが
この１０年があったからこそ➡
人間は 種族として
新たな力を得ることができた｡
And we will continue to prosper in the future.
そして これからも
強き種として繁栄し続けるのだ｡
陛下のお考えは
十分に承知しております｡
I understand your way of thinking, My Lord.
そのうえで
あえて申し上げるご無礼を➡
Please forgive me for what I am about to say.
お許しください｡
言ってみろ｡
Go on.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)神と魔の犠牲のうえに
成り立つ この繁栄➡
This prosperity built at the expense
of the gods and demons
私には
長きにわたるものとは思えません｡
will surely be unable to last.
ほう｡ わざわざ
こんな所まで来て言うことだ｡
Oh?
Being that you have come all this way to tell me,
ただの博愛主義とは
違うのだろうな｡
I am sure this is not merely blind altruism.
If this continues,
このままでは
必ず 第２第３の包帯悪魔が現れ➡
there will be more rag demons in our future
rising up to oppose mankind.
人間に牙をむくでしょう｡
何度も言うが
挑んでくるなら排除すればいい｡
I will say it again. We merely eliminate
those who would oppose us.
憎しみは 必ず連鎖し
より根深く 巨大になって➡
Hatred will beget hatred,
coming back to us much larger and insidious.
我々 人に返ってきます｡
安心しろ｡
Do not worry. I will acquire the power
to stave off this hatred you speak of.
私は その憎しみとやらを
しのぐ力を 必ず手に入れる｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)１０年前 世界が
滅びの危機に瀕したそのとき➡
Ten years ago, when the world
was on the brink of destruction,
I witnessed man, god, and demon
join hands to stand up against Bahamut.
人と神と魔が手を結び
バハムートに立ち向かう姿を➡
私は 確かに見ました｡➡
もし その協力がなかったら
人という種は➡
If not for that cooperation,
mankind would have surely perished.
あのときに滅んでいたでしょう｡
カイザル➡
Kaisar, are you content
with merely surviving extinction?
お前は 滅ばなければ
それでいいのか｡
Man, god, and demon joined hands?
人と神と魔が手を組んだ｡
それがどうした｡
What of it?
あの日
どれほどの命が失われたのか➡
Have you forgotten how many lives
were lost that day?
お前は忘れたのか｡
それとも
滅びの運命を避けられれば➡
Or are you not concerned about the victims
as long as we are able to avoid extinction?
犠牲はいとわないのか｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)違います！
-No, you are wrong!
-What am I wrong about?
何が違うというのだ｡ 神を拝み➡
Ten years ago, man bowed to the gods
and feared the demons!
魔を恐れた人類の成れの果てが
あの１０年前だ｡
人は変わらなければならないのだ｡
神にも魔にも➡
Mankind must change.
Change to become strong enough to confront
gods, demons, and even Bahamut.
バハムートにさえも左右されない
強い種族にな｡
それをなすことが
王である私の使命だ｡
And achieving this is my calling as king.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)確かに 人という種は➡
It may be true that mankind must change.
変わらなければ
ならないのかもしれません｡
しかし 陛下のおっしゃるように➡
But is merely possessing power,
as you suggest, really change?
力を持つことだけが
変化なのでしょうか？➡
私は そうは思いません｡ 必ず➡
I do not believe it is.
There has to be a path where
all three races can live in peace!
三種族が共に生きる道が
あるはずです｡
私は それを諦めない！
And I will never give up on it!
本当に甘い男だ｡
You truly are a naive man.
I am surprised you have been able
to survive for this long.
よく これまで生きてこられたな｡
お前は
お前の思うように生きてみよ｡
You live your life your way.
I will be doing what I feel is right.
私は 私の正義を貫くだけだ｡
However, if you should interfere with me,
だが
お前が私の邪魔になるのなら➡
I will eliminate you without mercy.
そのときは容赦なく排除する｡
≪(ﾍﾞﾙﾌｪｺﾞｰﾙ)アザゼル様
何を見ておられるのですか？
Lord Azazel,
what is it that you are looking upon?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)未来だ｡
The future.
(ﾍﾞﾙﾌｪｺﾞｰﾙ)いよいよですね｡
The time is close at hand.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)俺は
一瞬たりとも忘れたことはない｡
I haven't forgotten for a moment.
コキュートスが落ちた
あの日のことを｡➡
I still remember the day Cocytus fell.
必ず やってやる… 必ず｡
I will make them pay.
I vow it.
(ﾊﾝｻ)痛ぇ クワッ！ あたたっ…｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ･小声で)こら｡➡
Ow!
気をつけて｡
(ﾊﾝｻ･小声で)クワッ｡➡
Be careful.
前髪よけても 目をつぶってたら
分クワァりませんよね｡
Moving the hair out of the way won't matter
if his eyes are still closed.
(小声で)分かってる｡➡
I know that!
騒がないでくれよ｡
はい ごめんね｡➡
All right, here I go.
ごめんなさいね｡ はい 優しく…｡
I'm so sorry.
Softly now.
(２人･小声で)うん｡
(小声で)よし｡
All right.
What are you doing?
≫(小声で)何してんの？
べ べ… 別に｡
クワァいいなぁと思って➡
We were just admiring how cute you two are.
見つめてたんですよ｡
クワッ クワッ｡
変態！
うわぁ～～！
Pervert!
ドン！(激突音)
(ﾊﾝｻ)帰る｡
出てけ～！
うう～ あぁ…｡
Get out!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あぁ～ 痛っ…｡
It's okay, it's okay
I cast the usual spell
Stagnation, stagnation
My words and heart are at odds
Default
I've taken all the paint
And mixed up all the colors
Until you're left with me
So fragile
Yet strong
Close to overflowing
But not spilling
Because I'm incomplete
I won't amount to much
This is just a good luck charm
I'm not asking for your help
I was just clinging to you
Let's end it all today
I'm done living this pointless life
I've taken my last, pointless breath
To whom it may concern, see ya and goodbye
I killed the person I was yesterday
A new morning is coming
(ﾊﾝｻ)まったく
誰の馬車だと思ってんでしょうね｡
Honestly.
Whose carriage does she think this is?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)オッドアイの子供…｡
The child with two different colored eyes...
Your Majesty, why are you so exposed?
I've never seen you like this!
You should try being wild too.
-How unexpected of you!
-Don't be silly!
Next time on Rage of Bahamut: Virgin Soul,
"Anatean Holiday."
-I'm wild and exposed!
-You could say that again!
Baha Soul!!
Baha Baha Baha Soul!
Stay tuned for next time!